Shubhank Rastogi

Digital Product Manager

■ shubhankrastogi50@gmail.com (8849667034

https://rb.gy/er6kec

Highly Energetic Product manager with 3 + year of experience in Fintech Space. Collaborated with crossfunctional teams to plan, develop, manage and launch products from inception.

Blend technology skills with Agile experience, marketing orientation, and analytical abilities to prioritize and manage multiple projects within a specific timeline.

Education

Secondary High School

2015

Narsee Monjee Institute OF Management Studies

2020

- Bachelors in Electrical engineering (Gold medalist)
- GPA: 3.49/4

Narsee Monjee Institute OF Management Studies

2020

- MBA in Marketing (Gold Medalist)
- GPA: 3.49/4

Skills

- Agile Methodologies
- · Scrum management
- Product lifecycle management
- UI/UX design (Figma)
- Rest API

- Interpersonal Skills
- Collaboration skills
- Time Management
- Problem Solving Skills
- Communication

Experience

Svamaan Financial (JSW group) | Digital Product Manager

July 2023 - Present

- · Led the creation and launch of a user-friendly app for the Microfinance sector, aimed at improving the experience for current customers by enabling self-service options.
- Collaborated closely with the development team to prioritize tasks, monitor progress, and swiftly address any issues that arose.
- Managed the payments component, overseeing the integration process with external vendors to guarantee a seamless transaction experience via UPI intent
- Devised and implemented an improved onboarding procedure, streamlining user registration and account setup, which led to higher rates of customer acquisition and retention.
- Revamped the loan application process, making it simpler and more efficient by optimizing the Know Your Customer (KYC) journey with Straight Through Processing (STP), Digital KYC, and Manual KYC methods.
- Developed processes for cross-selling consumer durables and Bill Payment services, aimed at encouraging customers to embrace digital options.

Shubhank Rastogi

Digital Product Manager

■ shubhankrastogi50@gmail.com

& 8849667034

https://rb.gy/er6kec

Experience

5 Paisa Capital | Associate Product Manager

March 2022 - July 2023

- Leading the User Modification, reactivation and account closure functions with Growth vertical at 5 paisa.
- Leading the User Modification, reactivation and account closure functions with Growth vertical at 5 paisa.
- \bullet Achieved overall 80% approval rate by automating process and reduced task completion time by 50%
- Completed 4 new modification process and made live which were earlier completed through offline processes
- Implemented Account aggregator services for fetching customers bank statements which has an acceptance rate of 70%
- Introduced spouse account opening journey which has conversion rate of 25%
- Created 15 wireframe for new and existing processes.

ICICI Bank | Deputy Manager

Nov 2020 - March 2022

- Automate manual back-office Master setup through automation engine which helps in reducing Turn Around Time of master setup from 3 hours to 1.5 hours
- Successfully onboarded more than 50+ lenders(FI's) on FSCM platform
- Complete end to end product management of financial supply chain management product.
- Collaborate cross-functionally with multiple team to deliver new product solutions and enhance the existing portfolio.
- Integrating clients' ERP systems to banks via API thus eliminating manual intervention. This helps bank to save a Minimum of 2 manpower for each clients.